We also have an AI image generator, so this is a separate tool from QuillBot.
And as the name says, we can generate images over here.
Free online AI image generator, so I have an input.
I, for example, say, leopard hiding between trees.
So I want to say leopard dancing with the mouses, right?
And the style I wanted to be very real, so I wanted to have a style of realism.
And the aspect ratio, it's also provitable over here.
It's actually cool, right?
I want to put it on O2 because it doesn't matter at the end for me.
And I click on generate an image and wait to see how the result is going to look like.
So as you see, it has generated us two images.
This is what I'm seeing.
And if we wait a little bit, we will be able to see how they look like, right?
So we see this leopard over here dancing with these mouses.
Perfect. So it's also downloadable over here, as you see, I can even view it on full screen.
And that's pretty much all that we have with the image generator of QuillBot.